I post a lot of videos in the past few hours and sometimes I just get, um, I get wrapped up in just
like the frustration of how do you, how do these people do not see, how, how can these people say
these things, you know? And then I have to, um, I have to remind myself that, um, I have to just
focus on the people who understand. Like the last video I saw of Anas, he was in tears with his mic in
his hand reporting and he was so famished and exhausted. And like the people, people were
literally like behind him, like telling him to speak, speak, like we need you to speak on our
behalf. And, um, I will say that any of us who have, like, there are people who were completely
committed to the Palestine movement before October 7th. I was committed before October 7th.
However, those of us who really leaned in after October 7th and who have in a very relatively short
amount of time have become enveloped in this fight, we, we can't relate to other people.
I can't like have conversations like real meaningful conversations with, with anyone defending someone
like Kamala Harris or Joe Biden or Donald Trump or any of these people, like irregardless of all these
other scenarios, but just on the basic fact of their Zionists. Like I, like, and I had to catch myself
tonight because I'm like engaging in conversations with people who are legitimately and ardently
defending somebody who has called for and supported and excused a genocide. So I had to catch myself
because it is incredibly dehumanizing to even do that, to talk to those people. And you're like,
wait, what? No, no, no. What I should be doing right now is sending any vibration I can up,
praying, reading, committing myself as usual to trying to figure out a solution to how to bring an end to
what we are witnessing and, and, and hoping that it will continue to chain reaction to Sudan and to the Congo
and to all these other imperialist
genocides and oppressions that are happening.